I miss you, too,
but what are you doing up?
Isn't it, like, 3:00
in the morning in London?
Yeah, I've been having trouble
sleeping, too.
Alan suggested warm milk
and masturbation,
but that's his answer
for pretty much everything.
No, don't worry.
He's not gonna live here
forever.
More importantly, uh,
when are you coming back?
Ugh! Really, another week?
All right, that settles it.
I'm gonna heat up some milk.
Okay, all right.
Try to get some sleep.
I love you.
No, I love you more.
No, uh-uh, I love you more.
(makes kissing
sounds)
(Jake laughs)
(making
kissing sounds)
You got a problem with love?
Uh-uh.
No, no.
Sorry.
Oh, it's Jake and his friend.
No, he's not gonna stay here
forever, either.
All right, bye-bye.
Sweet dreams.
Sorry, we'll get out
of your way.
Nah, that's okay.
What are you guys doing?
Well, we were gonna
play a video game
on the big screen,
but if you're busy...
No, no, come on.
Nice.
Awesome.
Where's your dad?
Oh, he's out with
this guy's mom.
Yeah, they're picking
my grandma up
at the International House
of Old People.
I-Hoop.
She's in a rest home?
I guess
they're resting.
They don't move
very much.
Oh, except on pudding day.
Uh, then you could
get trampled.
Wow. Your dad's meeting
his girlfriend's mother.
That's a big step.
What's bigger than
boning each other?
Shut up!
Come on. We both
know they're doing it.
- We've heard them.
- Dude!
Oh, Alan!
Oh, Lyndsey!
Okay, quit it,
or I'm leaving.
Okay, fine.
And I'm taking my game.
I apologize.
Accepted.
It's nice you guys have a sense
of humor about that stuff.
So many kids of divorce are,
like, so angry all the time.
Yeah, well, it's kind of
hard to stay angry
when you smoke
as much pot as we do.
Truth.
When my dad left, I was, like,
really angry.
What did you do?
Just channeled my energy
into learning how
to program computers.
Made my first million
by the time I was 20.
- Oh, that's our plan, too.
- Totally.
Really? What language
do you guys code in?
Java? Perl? C-Plus-Plus?
Um...
Okay, maybe not a million.
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Ah.
♪ Men.
♪ Two and a Half Men 9x19 ♪
Palmdale, Ech
Original Air Date on March 19, 2012
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
(humming)
You're in a good mood.
I am.
Looking forward to
seeing your mother?
Not at all.
I'm high as a kite.
If I'm looking forward
to anything,
it's for that second
muscle relaxer to kick in.
I hear you. Unfortunately,
I can't do that with my mom.
I have to stay alert.
Dinner with her is like being
trapped in a box with a snake.
(laughs)
My mom's more like a hamster.
They seem cuddly,
but they eat their young.
Can't wait to meet her.
Oh, you'll love her.
Everybody loves her.
She's sweet, shy and charming.
Unless you happened
to come out of her uterus,
then you're part
of a balanced breakfast.
That bad, huh?
Yeah, and it's gotten worse
since my dad died.
Oh, she must have loved him
very much.
Nah, hated his guts.
She tried to kill him once.
You're kidding.
Yeah, they were playing golf.
He gave her a swing tip.
She hit him on the head
with a pitching wedge.
A-a pitching wedge?
It was the right club.
They were about 90 yards out.
Anyway, when he finally died
years later,
she decided
he was the love of her life,
moved into
a retirement community,
and put a "gone fishing sign"
on her hoo-ha.
Okay, guess I shouldn't
mention golf during dinner.
Mm.
Or fishing.
Yeah. You might also want
to stay away from politics,
religion or The Price Is Right.
The Price Is Right?
She misses Bob Barker.
Hates Drew Carey.
Oh, really?
I think he's a wonderful breath
of fresh air.
Do not say that.
♪ Men.
See, he's right
behind you!
Ah!
He's right behind you!
Move! Move! Duck!
Ah, ah, don't worry, Junior.
I got this!
Aah, crap.
Watch and learn.
Man, I used to be a lot better
at this.
I guess
I'm just out of practice.
That's 'cause
you got a girlfriend now.
Yeah. Your thumbs
have gotten weak.
That's why
I choose to be a bachelor.
Yeah, that's why.
So, what's the deal
with you and Zoey?
Are you gonna marry her?
I don't know.
I mean, I love her and all,
but I just got out
of a marriage.
Do I really want
to be back in one?
Hell, yeah.
She's hot.
It's not about how hot she is.
Oh, thank you, Jake.
It's about whether
she stays hot.
I mean, plus, there's some
serious stuff to consider.
She has a daughter,
so I'd be a stepdad.
My stepdad's a pretty cool guy.
I mean, he's always
slipping me money.
I think he feels bad
about replacing my dad.
Or about banging
your mom.
Shut up!
Mm, doesn't feel
so good, does it?
That's what
your mom said.
All right, can we please talk
about something other than sex?
Yes.
Okay.
But for the record,
I'm not a virgin.
Good to know.
Neither am I.
At least I think I'm not.
It was dark.
Could have been just leg.
But that still counts.
No, it doesn't.
Right?
Listen, if he thinks
he got laid,
what difference does it make?
Thank you.
♪ Men.
Mom, this is Alan.
Alan, this is my mom Jean.
Hi. Nice to
meet you.
How are you?
Uh, good, good.
Although I-I got to admit,
I'm-I'm a little nervous.
You know, I hope Mom likes me,
you know?
Relax, Alan.
When it comes to men,
Lyndsey has never
set the bar very high.
What's that supposed to mean?
I'm just saying that
you've always gone
for quantity
over quality.
It's a choice.
I'm not judging.
(sighs)
Oh.
Come on, muscle relaxers.
So, Alan,
do you have children?
Uh, I do. I have a son.
Mm.
That's good,
'cause even if Lyndsey
could bear another child,
I'm not sure
that would be the smartest move.
Mom!
Tell the truth.
Do you want another one
like Eldridge?
Let's just change
the subject.
Does anybody want
another Eldridge?
How are things
at Sunset Village?
Same old, same old.
Well, actually, some
of the same old died,
so we got some new old.
Oh, th's awful.
Not really.
If you get to their condo
before the relatives,
you can score
some great stuff.
Oh, Mom,
you're not saying...
How do you think
I got this lovely sweater?
It certainly wasn't
a Mother's Day gift.
(scoffs)
(laughs)
Well, uh,
if it comes up,
I'm a 40 regular.
(laughs)
So, Mom, do you want to do
anything special this weekend?
I'll be happy doing
whatever you want.
Oh, well, I-I thought maybe
tomorrow we could have lunch
at the Santa Monica Pier,
then go for a walk on the beach.
Oh, okay.
We don't have to.
No, that's fine.
I'm not afraid of
homeless people.
You know, your
daughter's a good lady.
You did a great
job with her, Jean.
Thanks.
But it was touch and go
for a while.
She told you about her
show business career, right?
Seriously, Mom? Really?
What? It was a
very nice movie--
if you like pornography.
Okay, I-I saw it, and-and
it wasn't pornography.
Well, it wasn't Mary Poppins.
So,
you guys graduate this year,
right?
I do.
I do, too.
Well, that's what
you said last year.
Yeah, but now, they're one
more year sicker of me.
So what are you gonna do now?
Well, we were hoping
we could work for you.
Doing what?
We'd be, like, consultants.
And what would you
be consulting about?
Well, that would be
our first consultation.
How about this?
We could tell you
what kids these days are into
and then develop killer apps
to target that geographic.
Demographic.
No, Republican kids, too.
Mm.
All right, Consultants,
tell me some of your app ideas.
Okay, well, you know, uh,
when you take a picture of
your junk and send it to a girl?
Um... no.
But I understand the concept.
Okay, okay, well, this app
makes your junk look bigger.
And you can customize it.
You can customize your junk?
Yeah, you know,
like silly hats,
glasses, little messages.
"Wish you were here."
Get it? Get it?
Yeah, I get it.
So, it's like Photoshop,
but for your junk.
We call it Junkshop.
It's a good name.
What do you do
if you already got big junk?
Oh, way ahead of you.
Tell him about Boobshop.
All right, you know
how girls always complain
about one boob being bigger
than the other?
Oh, thank God,
she's asleep.
I don't think
I can last four days.
Every word out of her mouth
pushes my buttons.
Yeah, I saw.
She's like a ninja mom.
She sneaks in,
destroys your will to live,
and then,
disappears without a trace.
So I'm not crazy?
Oh, no, not at all.
Oh.
In fact, it kind of makes me
grateful for my mom.
What do you mean?
Well, there's no sneaking
and stabbing in the back.
She just walks right up to you,
and hits you in the face
with a lead pipe.
(laughs)
I wonder what would happen
if we put them
in the same room together.
Uh. Momageddon.
(laughing)
Although... it wouldn't be
the worst idea in the world.
What?!
Well, think about it.
They're around the same age,
they're single,
they're both deeply disappointed
in their children
and their children's children.
They might hit it off.
And if they did,
it might give us a break.
You know what? Tell you what--
I will call my mom
and try to set up a dinner.
Oh, Alan,
that would
be wonderful. Mm.
I owe you one.
You still owe me one
from my birthday.
(sighs) Well...
if she wasn't here,
I'd be steering this car
with the back
of my head right now.
Looks like she's
sleeping pretty good.
Oh, what the hell?
Scoot your seat back.
ALAN:
Yay!
♪ Men.
Hey, what you doing?
Absolutely nothing.
I'm bored out of my mind.
Oh, well, Lyndsey and I
are having dinner with our moms.
You're welcome to join us.
A two-mom dinner?
You can say no.
No. God, no.
I get you.
I don't want to go, either.
Why are you
doing it?
Are you thinking
about getting married?
Um, to answer your questions
in reverse order:
not at the moment and oral sex.
Night.
Oral sex.
Time to warm up the old milk.
Oh, great, Amy.
We'll be there.
What's going on?
Just got invited
to a slammin' party
in the Valley.
Cool.
Can we borrow your car?
Uh, all right, let me think.
Two potheads want to borrow
my $100,000 car
to go to a slammin' party
in the Valley.
Sounds like a no.
Wait, wait, wait.
Let's hear him out.
It's a no!
I'll give you guys a ride.
- Oh, sweet.
- Thanks.
What you got going on
with the water?
Oh, we had another idea
for an app.
Let me guess-- Sinkshop.
Oh, no, no.
Okay, imagine the app
is on my phone.
- All right.
- Go ahead.
(inhales deeply)
JAKE:
Now, all I do
is press this button,
and our app will tell you
exactly how long you can
hold your breath underwater.
That's clever.
Thanks.
How is it different
than the stopwatch
that's already
on your phone?
The what?
See this
little clock?
Oh.
Damn.
How long?
So this is nice, huh?
Lovely.
I can't remember
how long it's been
since the last time
you called me to have dinner.
Oh, come on. It hasn't
been that long.
Oh, please.
Jake was still cute.
Guess it has been awhile.
So what's up with this dinner?
Why are you finally allowing me
to meet your girlfriend?
First of all, I wasn't
disallowing you
from meeting her;
I was just, uh...
avoiding it as long as possible.
Uh, but things
are more serious between us now,
and I thought it might be nice
for you two
to get to know each other.
- All right.
- And her mother might come along.
Her mother?
Yeah, she's, uh,
in town visiting.
I thought you two
might hit it off.
Alan, you know
I don't like old people.
I do know, but you'll like her.
She's young at heart,
like you.
I'm young everywhere--
all the parts.
Sure.
What I haven't replaced,
I've had tightened,
bleached or trimmed.
Got it.
So where's
the old biddy live?
Palmdale.
Palmdale, ech.
Is she married?
Uh, widow.
How'd her husband die?
Heart attack.
Boring.
She did actually try
to kill him once.
Oh.
Well, at least we have
something in common.
Sure you gave me
the right address?
Yeah.
1478 Amy Lane.
Wait a sec.
Isn't Amy Lane the name
of the chick having the party?
It may not be Amy Lane.
But we're on
Amy Lane.
An amazing coincidence, huh?
Is there somebody
you guys can call?
I mean,
I can call Amy Lane.
If that is, in fact,
her real name.
(thud)
Evelyn, Alan tells me
you do a lot of traveling.
Yes. I love it.
The classical architecture,
the exotic cuisine,
the uncircumcised men.
(gags)
Although one could make a case
that falls under
"exotic cuisine."
(whispering): Just like you and
Alan in the car.
Do you guys travel much?
Not anymore.
But when my husband was alive,
we went everywhere.
Six Flags, Epcot, Dollywood.
Charming.
Real globe-trotter.
(chuckles)
Speaking of which, I once slept
with Meadowlark Lemon.
Let me tell you,
basketballs weren't
the only thing he could spin.
(whispering):
I'm so sorry.
I hope this is it.
They have a balloon
on the mailbox
that says party.
Mm.
(doorbell rings)
Yeah?
Uh, is this
where the party is?
Oh, you saw the balloon, huh?
Come on in.
Okay.
Oh, hang on.
Hang on. Excuse us.
Don't you pay attention
in health class?
What are you
talking about?
Stranger danger.
No, he seems okay.
You guys like to wrestle?
Let's book it, dude.
Yeah. Walden!
Don't go!
Always a bridesmaid.
Really, Alan?
Why don't I get this?
Well, you got to admit
my plan worked.
They hit it off and left us
pretty much unscathed.
Plus, thanks to your mom,
my mom can now go back
to her retirement community
and show all her girlfriends
what happens
when you Google "Santorum."
(both laughing)
Lyndsey, will you take me
to get a tramp stamp?
What?
It's a cute little tattoo
right here.
Evelyn has one.
You do?
I got it in Singapore.
The Chinese characters for:
"Thank you. Come again."
All right, well,
we're done here.
Why don't we head home?
I don't want
to go home.
Evelyn says there's a place
right down the street
where they have music
and dancing.
Oh, I don't think so.
It's getting kind of late.
Yeah, we both have
to work in the morning.
I don't.
Neither do I.
Why don't you two fuddy-duddies
run along
and let Jean and I
have some fun?
How will you get home?
Alan, I made it from Brunei
to Morocco with nothing
but the clothes on my back
and a tube of lubricant.
I think I can get us
from Tarzana to Sherman Oaks.
(giggling):
Isn't she a hoot?
All right,
if you're sure.
Let's go.
You think we'll find
some cute fellas to dance with?
Oh, Jean, Jean, Jean.
We're not going
to dance.
♪ Men.
Should have written
the address down, dude.
I did write it down.
She must have told it
to me wrong.
Or maybe you
heard it wrong.
If only there was an app that
could capture the spoken word.
(button clicks)
(on phone): If only there was an app that
could capture the spoken word.
Don't mock us, man.
(button clicks)
Hi, Jake.
Hi, Eldridge.
- Hey.
- Hi.
I bet they were
at the party.
Yeah, maybe they can
tell us where it is.
Oh, good thinking.
I'll text 'em.
Wait, I don't have
their numbers.
Man, we're never going
to find this party.
Okay.
Let me ask you a question.
If you had made it to the party,
what would you have done there?
Try to hook up
with some chicks.
Why don't you hook up with them?
Right there--
that's why you're rich.
Would you mind very much if
we, you know, blew you off?
I would worry about
you if you didn't.
- Bye.
- Later.
ELDRIDGE:
Hello, ladies.
JAKE: Mind if we
hook up with you?
♪ Men.
Morning.
Oh, morning.
You and Evelyn have a
good time last night?
Fantastic.
Mm.
I adore your mother.
(chuckling): That's only because
you just met her.
I don't know, I think I got
to know her pretty well.
Good morning,
darling.
Hi, Peaches.
Once again,
I'm so, so sorry.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
www.tvsubtitles.net